David Braga Vieira

Front End Web Developer

Auckland, New Zealand
021 140 6539

E bragav.david@gmail.com

david-braga

。 <u>David Braga V.</u>

ABOUT ME

Originally from Brazil, I have been living in and loving Aotearoa for almost 10 years now.

I have a passion for learning and since I started my first online HTML, CSS and JS courses in 2019 I can't get enough of it.

Recently, I have completed a Software Development Bootcamp and after this life changing experience I am a Software Developer keen to continue evolving and learning.

I am an active person who enjoys many kinds of sports and outdoor activities in my free time.

I have a background in Hospitality which gave me the ability to work well under pressure and great Interpersonal Skills. It also helped me improve my attention to details.

I also worked as an abseiler doing building maintenance and this experience taught me the importance of working in a team and meeting deadlines.

SKILLS

Teamplayer

Attention to detail

Enthusiastic

Self-Motivated

TECHNOLOGY

HTML

CSS

Javascript

Node Js.

GitHub

ReactJs

Redux

ExpressJs

EXPERIENCE

Enspiral Dev Academy, Remote— Apprenticeship

AUG 2021 - DEC 2021

- Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp.
- More than 700 hours coding on multiple projects in a team environment following Agile principles replicating real life conditions.

CitySide Properties Ltd, Auckland — Height Technician/ Team leader

JUN 2017 - AUG 2021

- General building maintenance via abseil.
- Always working in teams following safety standards and making sure the jobs were done on time.

LANGUAGES

Portuguese

English

Spanish

Swiss Belsuites Victoria Park, Auckland — Hotel Receptionist

FEB 2017 - JUN 2017

 Responsible for greeting and checking- in and checkingout guests, liaising with other departments, making bookings, night auditing and answering phone calls and replying to emails.

Black Sheep Backpackers, Queentown — Front Desk

DEC 2014 - DEC 2016

• Check-in and check-out of guests, make bookings, liaise with the Director and the Housekeeping team.

EDUCATION

Enspiral Dev Academy, Auckland, NZ — Full Stack Web Development Certificate

AUG 2021 - DEC 2021

Crown Institute, Auckland, NZ — Travel and Tourism Diploma

FEB 2013 - JUN 2013

IESB - Higher Education Institute of Brasilia, Brasilia, BR —

Travel and Tourism Bachelor Degree

FEB 2000 - DEC 2004

REFERENCES

Available upon request.